That Navi General Insurance which
was first known as Dedication General Insurance,
this is Holi and most importantly Navi Technologies
and its operations were of the year in India
in November 2017 Ravi Jain Forum of newly launched
health insurance products you can buy in Navi Health
Insurance so I will give you details about it
today we will cover red chilli
or input but not required and
how you can buy it before sharing the video
I would like to thank you yes I have taken pill
quantity and I am the
Shraddha of cleanliness and I will bring new videos of Vikas so that you can
like your summary and
yes I drove my car worldwide Vikas rides a
lot, the rating is
very good if you go to office send it, so
first we will talk about the basic eligibility
minimum instigators policy in this is for
children maximum entries for children
is 30yrs means 34yrs children can
enroll in the policy minimum entry adult
city near maximum entries 1872 this
policy is involved in your life  Which is your
life every month quality but after the most emphasis you
cannot add animals
chilli powder solar maximum is 60 crores
so individual and family both of these
polythene both are absolutely
polytechnic and wali friend you friend seriously
options are available there is something unique in it which
you will not find any shame in other policies
which is your option here if you
take a policy of Agra Gwalior then you have hit option
that you have to make a one time payment upfront
second option you can make payment half yearly quarterly also
without any
extra point if you take a policy of two years and share then
you will have to make a one time
payment upfront room rent which is the
eligibility for single room you are single you
can take Priyanka hospitalization
minimum coastal city maximum is late to come so in this there are
different types of players
airplane 12345 though you will see
in the video so according to that you choose to make
and this will be your favorite hospitalization
limit listen buy on minimum side
when you suicide well Delhi
If you take a room in the room, then it
gives you telecast benefits. Features at that
point MG Road Ambulance is news of
Spiritual Ayurveda, AYUSH, Ayurvedic, Unani,
Siddha and Homeopathy.
Hospitalization is the word for hospitalization of your time and
secondly, hospitalization means
going to the hospital at home, if you get treatment at home for 3 consecutive
days, then you get the
right to hospitalization.
You have time, taste and smell and
transplant, excise officer online after
consultation, basically this line is
taken through the mobile application, this is the
Naveen Health Insurance
application, you
can go there and select your request, you will get
options and you can talk to the sister, so
this mobile patient has online
consultation given weapon, you can convert if you
want to convert, you can convert, plus
a decade treatment cover is in the policy, which means it is
difficult,
because of the batsman of science and technology, you do not get 24-hour
hospitalization medicine, if
you  You should definitely come home after commenting,
half of them are cleaned, so the clothes for
example, Mary, should be set before the patients
directly, otherwise you have to do it.
Now here you go in the morning and you get
discharged in the evening, then in the medical test, the
policy of opposing Modi is
approved by the Additional Commissioner.
In case of accidental hospitalization, suppose someone has an
experience, he is your light,
then there is always the
traditional Someshwar inbuilt in the policy,
which is available, there is automatic
restoration, that is, if your weight decreases to 108, then
you
can automatically apply the response policy and press the best is
always that and you can limit it with something, there is a
button of diabetes cancer also,
in this line there is a
waiting period for the minimum respect of the button addictions, that means you keep
getting a certificate in the policy.
Totally mutton expenses are limited in it, there is a limit of
meter roti, basically two deliveries or two
terminations of pregnancy, there is a card
and its limited thirty thousand rupees  For
delivery newborn baby button one day
senses to 1000 the insurance company will pay
your date of birth now after AB year
you can click on it with the letter S
but it would have been ₹2000 I would like to tell you
that this is maternity Hanuman expenses this
exile will not happen forever this
3000 1000 is the limit that is being given on it the
first item on the cross button
policy long hospitalization marital
is available that we are telling all the maritime this over
and above hospitalization quick facts about
you on that suppose
someone was in a hunger strike more than a dozen times
if his
hospitalization is on mode then in that case the
insurance company equity slum sun tan
effective one a politician emergency air
ambulance birthday now ₹5 a let's go to
balance benefits so balance benefits is
that your health and balance should be taken care of on
that the insurance company kisses you like a
sick person attacks here  If
you have an entry preventive health checkup in your
insurance policy, if
you have a deductible above zero and are enrolled in the policy, then
you get a complimentary business setup through
which Rajpal Dil list
is prescribed play store and this decision has to be taken by the
insurance company,
so they are network less Manish, you can get your test done,
after this the second step after getting the test done is to
add status report, if
your test report is correct, if your test report is correct, there is
no action, it is quite clear, it is being
set, that is the criteria function, then
you are given a report on the basis of help centers,
send account details on the side,
Mohanlal, if you use that, then
you will get back the
bulk pack to your criteria, I have
shared that chart with you, so if you right
click on a modern chart,
you will get a five percent account and
invented the special status report
using factors that and you send it,
synchronize it with the new health insurance application,
then you get the benefits on that page,
if you submit some number of work  If you do Delhi, then
you will get work on this basis. The
previous requirement is
Forces Pandey minimum today. This will make you
eligible for the work.
Next, Animal Prints Art Fashion
Treatment Benefit, this is your speed
actions, that is, the infection that occurs
after being admitted to the hospital, there is a sensor and question from Sibal,
you should get any diagnostic test done for consultation, they
call it option department
and they call patient express, then they will check the
limit in the rotation policy in the specific water policy, you can take it for a policy like Zor
Chili or 250 Animal Planet
Neptune and it is tax free, so like
you have to inform the insurance company
with which doctor you want to take it, this will be your
pencil and the center in Bangalore will
decide accordingly, so
their small is here in the same way
so that they will give you, so I will share with you the
5 lines on Nuclear
Plant 2345 Trans, this is basic astrology,
what is the news about the hospitalization
expenses in line 12345
Modern money will sink in parties is always busy
hospitalization expenses plan has
husband plant them directly plant free
hazel ko 16550
hospitalization in the sixth day plan
2011 0 plan for advance telecast co
share room occupancy hydride take then
you are looking for work then it gives you
poison in logic plant 125 emergency road
ambulance sa but also mentioned in the
pipeline obscene ayush treatment plant
1234 is not back cover allu shipment of a
government official notification reserved to be
established in the pipeline 12345
organ donor expansion plan 12345
on all transactions online after consultation
which is unlimited by removing all your
alarms flat no claim bonus
actually line 3500 maximum 21 people
to plants that he 520 always maximum
hundred percent plants in tapasya time
4 mushroom pimple plan for me if  Pass
updates always maximum hundred percent
plan 5 minutes 60% they always maximum up
to five 20%
if you will
use it, okay
after that
you will
not have to here and
automatically time on 12345 if you MS Word then
automatically
soon
12345 unlimited
subscribe button
play again
that the palace of non-tablet rituals of Turkish resource
1234 is not covered in the plan file
discovered to be punished for long
hospitalization excise help above
hospitalized are this benefit is given in
which airplane 1234 is not commented
then there is a button in it this panacea is like this
mask button plan 123 code word in
flights of president and chief has first
fit shop state in diagnostic
flying was not want to make suit is not there
plan free ₹5000 for members under
individual and 1000 meter plan for me
duty nahi hai plan
phase and member in  Individual Darkness
Duty Policy All these skin diseases
that you have before taking the policy do
not happen to them. There are lieutenants
taking the juice of 2012 Pacific International Meeting,
which feel like virus lokrang,
like spoon castor oil,
coriander replacements. All these policies have
aunty in mind. 100 blend ones
are not covered for two years and 12345
waiting till is Maniar's super dance
is available, as you have seen in these from flight to flight,
you can choose your super dance as per your need, what do
you want, you were thinking
what is this, you can
definitely subscribe and its premium will
vary from that vest, so
you will download an application, you can
also see the premium calculation from there,
and if you want to take Bliss of Policy,
Individual Family Floater, from that
you will get pregnancy
and I am putting its positive voting
in my description box for
your reference, you can see it and any of
your questions on without election health
insurance please  Tell me or dacoit
remind, if you have not yet subscribed to our channel
then subscribe, I
promise you that you will keep
getting information about the elements, you will still go to the
next video, how do you want to see it,
thank you so much, you too have a fan, our
phone number is available below, you
can connect and Vipin Sharma can set up a comment section, see you
soon in the next video,
bye-bye
construction, then don't give up somewhere, construction keeps happening
in Delhi and lodged a
complaint about Vikas Research, someone's dream
house is being built, but if he makes a
video here, that is, early morning, then it is
fine, if you cannot make it on the table, that is
[Music]